{"question":"633490 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9746", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"317250 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6750", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85470 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2310", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"53536 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1912", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"222384 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4633", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"443762 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9647", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24346 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"658", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"384146 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8351", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196695 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4371", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"375375 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4875", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69102 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1047", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"575190 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7470", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"789536 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8972", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"241032 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2904", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99549 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1229", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"310695 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4035", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178756 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6164", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"420825 : 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4525", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"328860 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3654", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"483420 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6906", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74048 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1157", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"372020 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4180", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"356865 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9645", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100386 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2574", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"288512 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4508", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18986 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"863", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"526234 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6119", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"164592 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4572", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"165002 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4853", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13748 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"491", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"170832 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3559", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"530630 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5645", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15600 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"260", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"206528 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7376", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"144882 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2683", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"264112 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3884", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"411584 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6976", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"208806 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5354", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3893 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"229", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"506292 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"674053 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6949", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267331 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6217", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"866712 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9849", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76626 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2322", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26040 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1860", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"578350 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6725", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"524370 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7945", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"560748 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6756", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"260256 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5422", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"346112 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5408", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"146140 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7307", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"457479 : 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4621", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125132 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8938", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"478744 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8549", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198940 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4060", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"201871 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8777", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19824 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"944", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"309471 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7197", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"162900 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9050", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"263908 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3881", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60400 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1510", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"68105 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1285", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67632 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2818", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117852 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4209", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"390540 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6509", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137242 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9803", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"352718 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"272426 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3538", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"257560 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2740", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54978 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"714", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"280868 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5732", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"271712 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4852", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153594 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2898", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"335996 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4421", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51930 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"577", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117219 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2859", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30832 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"752", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50670 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"563", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42501 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1371", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118360 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1345", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123120 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3078", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154336 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2968", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"381465 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6055", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"783990 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8711", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75081 : 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"863", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"480928 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"311400 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4325", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"415008 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4323", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"255930 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2694", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"405888 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9664", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"473440 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98098 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3773", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"494312 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9506", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19512 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1084", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23880 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1990", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"741000 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9880", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"209608 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7486", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56848 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"836", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21384 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"324", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102882 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3957", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"161882 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5222", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"163419 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8601", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"239944 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2696", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"298966 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3602", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98800 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5200", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"194675 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2995", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130680 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3630", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"453815 : 85 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5339", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12528 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"448888 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5101", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30960 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10184 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"205790 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15576 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"649", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"678300 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9044", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10137 : 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"109", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110604 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2127", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196084 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7003", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25088 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"784", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191815 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2951", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"207060 : 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"630800 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6640", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"43624 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"574", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"667888 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8788", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"186233 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3053", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"223470 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3438", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"126350 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1330", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"186921 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2967", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"168345 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6235", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102816 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3808", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60720 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4048", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"548169 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9291", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54126 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1746", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"182004 : 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2092", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"532620 : 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"88400 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"504152 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7414", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99015 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1435", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69079 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1867", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"598381 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8197", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40411 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1757", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"654904 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"145936 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9121", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"222912 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6966", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"382739 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5243", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"273980 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3914", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211792 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3472", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"761592 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9764", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93852 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"758527 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9851", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64519 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"709", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240955 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3707", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"681375 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9875", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73770 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2459", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34890 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1163", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240540 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3165", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131511 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2229", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"242406 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3618", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"544812 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6564", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5141 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"53", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"257646 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5601", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93124 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3004", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"744390 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"569835 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8505", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"616492 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6701", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5141 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"53", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55935 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1695", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141208 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7432", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"559874 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5713", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"241296 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5027", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"230218 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3902", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13488 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"843", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111111 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2849", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"241992 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6722", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140658 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2758", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198696 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8279", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116316 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1436", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124632 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2308", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"488622 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6603", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"134060 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6703", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18872 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"674", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160678 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3493", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"226413 : 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2287", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"492975 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6573", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158640 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2644", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"452720 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5659", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"126555 : 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9735", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"285705 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4535", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77872 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1256", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"191884 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2156", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52416 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1456", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"135360 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6768", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"466250 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9325", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76080 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85384 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1642", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55770 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2535", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"237798 : 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2402", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93806 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5518", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"586224 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9936", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"312405 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5295", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"560700 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"280227 : 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3221", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"250654 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5449", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109840 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1373", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"343617 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7311", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106425 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1935", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2002 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"77", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"496120 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6280", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"274932 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4364", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47073 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"923", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111000 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3000", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12816 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1068", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"308142 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5406", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"285246 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7314", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38740 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"745", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"272706 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6342", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47920 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2995", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66263 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"989", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"107736 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1608", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"454477 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7703", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"186576 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7774", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37000 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"740", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"133440 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2085", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48768 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"762", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"562115 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5917", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"282360 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3620", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"499577 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6019", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109404 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6078", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"816672 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8507", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"448957 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5683", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"223032 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9293", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4410 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"315", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"99600 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6640", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37726 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1451", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"177570 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9865", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"497394 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8154", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"362204 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7874", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"322500 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65070 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2410", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59328 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1854", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"422370 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9386", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30728 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54928 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3433", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30132 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2511", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100110 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6674", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"222028 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4724", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"503616 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5246", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"300560 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8840", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39633 : 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3603", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"249018 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3773", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25461 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"369", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"323187 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6337", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75789 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1203", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"176448 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1838", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"685088 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8672", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85065 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5671", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86775 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2225", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"660348 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8466", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13440 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"336", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"717314 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7631", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"137334 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2922", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"136305 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3495", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64700 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1294", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200141 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3281", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"568639 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8009", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24864 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1184", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"177654 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3063", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"425250 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6075", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"685542 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7293", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"442860 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8052", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104941 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6173", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"213690 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7123", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13425 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"537", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"292416 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6092", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198072 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7074", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"203087 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7003", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"336019 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4603", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"351728 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3952", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"502788 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9669", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11830 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"338", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26928 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1122", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"543456 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7548", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"642880 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9184", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13005 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"289", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95452 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3409", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"516439 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6707", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"565130 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9115", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"377685 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5995", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"627480 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8715", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101920 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1960", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600120 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"195024 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3824", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"230900 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4618", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"578935 : 85 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6811", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"514476 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8298", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26802 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1489", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"167220 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1858", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52920 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3780", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"582594 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6546", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160182 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8899", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45530 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1570", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"247104 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2808", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"192740 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"345483 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5007", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"231472 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3404", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2808 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"72", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110376 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1971", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66352 : 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5104", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"426303 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5263", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"459774 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5607", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92170 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3545", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"432124 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7084", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"632996 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6734", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84240 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"936", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140828 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8284", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178464 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4576", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158584 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3688", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95368 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6812", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40820 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2041", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27740 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"365", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26972 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"613", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"729640 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9860", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48640 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1520", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33288 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"456", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"370523 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6991", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38583 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1429", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"448293 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5037", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"247408 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4418", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"138898 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"443196 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8523", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97442 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1174", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"543870 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6043", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"593704 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6316", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80940 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1420", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63200 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1264", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"325040 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4780", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"227032 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3068", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"109908 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2556", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"492704 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5536", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"360003 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4557", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105179 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6187", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"506678 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6847", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"307285 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8305", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84720 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1412", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58248 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3236", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121845 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8123", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"325512 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9864", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"288512 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9016", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125560 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1720", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108864 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2268", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"352751 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7199", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154780 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2180", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"375191 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9151", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140744 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1928", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"274620 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5970", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119910 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3426", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267540 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4459", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50585 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"755", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"451512 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6271", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"321048 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8918", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"372638 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8666", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38544 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"803", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"359252 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4727", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"101244 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4602", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"416020 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9455", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158289 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2777", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"503503 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5533", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57792 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1204", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"251711 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6803", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"430900 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8618", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"534184 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9539", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"903830 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9514", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80172 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1572", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"402636 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5162", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"204765 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4015", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"447720 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6888", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8280 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"120", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"655218 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7362", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"199038 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4739", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13695 : 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1245", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"204000 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4250", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76976 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4811", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240042 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3637", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"201391 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"121075 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4843", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"801705 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8439", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"183610 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5246", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"741612 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8061", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"438242 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9527", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96348 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8177 : 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"629", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"345891 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3801", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21360 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"712", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37632 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"784", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"897024 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9344", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108264 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4164", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93886 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2041", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"66105 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1695", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"248092 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9542", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"237728 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6256", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"255696 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5327", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"76084 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"827", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"327745 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5555", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"291772 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4706", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"647130 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9805", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"209208 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9096", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"465300 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6204", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123336 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1713", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240240 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4004", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90216 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3759", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"216894 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5862", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"91182 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6513", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"282750 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3770", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"340816 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5012", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"498000 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6225", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"386920 : 85 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4552", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"352547 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7501", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"581102 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6757", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"298110 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9937", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"280872 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3384", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"186410 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5326", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"326710 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8830", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19844 : 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1804", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"317775 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3345", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27120 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1695", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"584808 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6962", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"131958 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7331", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24112 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"274", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102486 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5394", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30576 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2548", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"322044 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6852", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"613392 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7864", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119459 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7027", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72156 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3436", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"721112 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9128", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"155652 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3052", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"753228 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8967", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45764 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1346", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178552 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2029", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96530 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2758", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13091 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"689", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8316 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"297", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211497 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7293", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158625 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5875", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"482196 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6182", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"957 : 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"622844 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6626", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"894069 : 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9031", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"190728 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5298", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"262037 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3911", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"310176 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4308", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6465 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"431", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78570 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"810", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"388896 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8102", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"333143 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4217", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"452848 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5456", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"58080 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"726", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"102486 : 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1178", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154632 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3032", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"611490 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9265", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"671202 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6849", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"387435 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5615", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"492936 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6486", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"169890 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5663", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"427630 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6109", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8170 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"215", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42172 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"811", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12240 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"170", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"422172 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5212", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51576 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1842", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"277380 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4623", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"332906 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7742", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"29491 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"383", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8300 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"415", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95854 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4357", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63470 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1154", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"317360 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7934", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267989 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9241", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"255094 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5206", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113856 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7116", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"666761 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9391", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"883980 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9822", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"533414 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5443", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"145420 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7271", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"79400 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"195492 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5924", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"689850 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7665", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"470351 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9599", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"257803 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2833", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"505725 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9195", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"824964 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9821", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"31108 : 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2828", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65156 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4654", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113043 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5383", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198702 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3154", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"171108 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9506", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"418080 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6968", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"512533 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7021", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"304110 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3379", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"211590 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7053", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"244545 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6987", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"78186 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"942", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"581248 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9082", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"504804 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8556", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"292480 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4570", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"432880 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7730", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"343580 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8380", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1067 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"11", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106132 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4082", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"354613 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7237", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6050 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"110", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30745 : 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2365", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19160 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"958", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"624312 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6786", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"526320 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6120", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12672 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"176", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"437874 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7682", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"190820 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3290", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"180370 : 85 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2122", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"520854 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5541", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85150 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3406", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104510 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2986", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30030 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2145", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"237678 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5659", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69377 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1309", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"279496 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3038", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24416 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"436", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45291 : 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"487", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35280 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"980", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69888 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"768", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"163821 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5649", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"344736 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8208", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"256768 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7552", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"538000 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6725", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"797306 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9271", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"288720 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6416", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"795804 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9588", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"873082 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8909", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117208 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8372", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113390 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6670", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"463540 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6020", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"263004 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4242", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"546048 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6912", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"335070 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7446", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"251804 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8993", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55212 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"642", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104591 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2551", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115280 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2882", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59922 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3329", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"321139 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3529", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"159274 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1642", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"391461 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7989", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"94511 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3259", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85425 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1275", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23480 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"587", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"703000 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9250", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"96968 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2108", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48466 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2203", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34840 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"670", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"186505 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3391", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"177332 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2062", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"171990 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4095", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"483408 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8952", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108580 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1220", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36585 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"813", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67508 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2411", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77248 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4544", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"309374 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4238", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"149931 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1851", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"474214 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7774", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"677740 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9682", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"237500 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3125", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"843206 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9266", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60272 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3767", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"273372 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6213", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"531272 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9487", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"166075 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4745", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"433924 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5228", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600066 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8109", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"678193 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8171", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5920 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"80", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"335479 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9067", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16992 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"288", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"615271 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6343", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"266623 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6503", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"293246 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7717", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"510750 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6810", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13144 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"212", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"69300 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1100", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4275 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"285", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"409332 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5316", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"380864 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8656", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33422 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1966", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"203347 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4729", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"174725 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6989", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"26622 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"493", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7824 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"163", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"391564 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7388", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"317088 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8808", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"358061 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8327", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39948 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3329", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19360 : 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1760", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"146433 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2569", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"119196 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2772", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"162540 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2709", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"212936 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2476", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"325080 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3870", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"117783 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1707", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10260 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"228", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"132192 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2592", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"569114 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"635663 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8953", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"454916 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9284", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"168982 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7681", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"250750 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4250", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"255712 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7991", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"315350 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9010", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"408268 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103037 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5423", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"477620 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9185", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"195377 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2147", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"139455 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5165", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110808 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5832", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"388751 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6589", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93206 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1607", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130970 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3742", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"686566 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7078", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"84420 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1005", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"224604 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3303", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14553 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"189", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"854462 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8719", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"44010 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2445", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"338523 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5939", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"172118 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2099", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"152928 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6372", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127875 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8525", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"403793 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4537", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"450736 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8668", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38934 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"618", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"516320 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9220", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"488547 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8571", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"366196 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4412", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"268812 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9956", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"236845 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6767", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"501495 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7485", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"243600 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8400", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"393689 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5393", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"92344 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6596", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1404 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"39", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"81539 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1217", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"284398 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5366", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"151179 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2191", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"397978 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4061", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45999 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2421", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108414 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5706", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"527204 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7753", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160361 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9433", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73595 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1795", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"279756 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4908", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"571620 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8166", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"568872 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7901", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"468544 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7321", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80906 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5779", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93940 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6710", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11325 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"453", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"164968 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4852", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"631180 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8305", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"256536 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56376 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1944", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"957068 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9766", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"692037 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9747", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"85904 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6136", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"219667 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4483", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90018 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1667", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"143783 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2437", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"326976 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3406", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"113709 : 87 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1307", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"208010 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3410", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"288532 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5444", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"640112 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7274", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90720 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5670", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"316305 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5751", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"274758 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3982", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11744 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"367", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"174817 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2963", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"764126 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8129", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15774 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"239", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127644 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1934", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"77740 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"845", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32178 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1038", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"55539 : 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5049", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6580 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"70", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"197120 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2464", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"97384 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3478", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"505505 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5555", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36480 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"640", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"496614 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6711", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"552475 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7175", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"118888 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47117 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"889", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"186384 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2824", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"47187 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"749", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"353160 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4360", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"339958 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7906", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32952 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2746", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104286 : 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8022", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"95446 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3671", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"365566 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3889", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93960 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1160", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"86160 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2154", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"758472 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8619", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"87115 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2489", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"304928 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5864", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"278964 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7749", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"203338 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5351", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"34068 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1002", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"355266 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8262", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"422740 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"39308 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1268", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"122853 : 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1321", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20808 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1224", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"458370 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5093", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"417352 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8026", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38608 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"508", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"257244 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9894", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"308112 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5502", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"515968 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8896", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"329630 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4709", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"350460 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6490", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128960 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6448", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"185696 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5803", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"639236 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8411", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"204710 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9305", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72848 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2512", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"937699 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9667", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"495648 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5163", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"149904 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3123", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33210 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"810", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267979 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3011", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"291118 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3097", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"548757 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7953", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"163804 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5284", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"299376 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9072", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11584 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"724", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19292 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"364", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"203013 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2781", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62766 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3487", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"445154 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6098", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"396011 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5143", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"274464 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2859", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"147591 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6417", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"262675 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3325", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"305096 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3467", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"567000 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9000", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"469566 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8238", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5168 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"152", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"393250 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6050", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"23856 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1988", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114767 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2669", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"242712 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6742", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"556339 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6251", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"359328 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6304", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"270156 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5748", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"674388 : 99 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6812", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"214430 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2615", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"770308 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9394", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30363 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1047", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100362 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2334", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"306600 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80066 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"931", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"397880 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9947", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200320 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6260", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"178728 : 88 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2031", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"204720 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5118", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"110832 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2309", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"196692 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5316", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35496 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1479", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"337194 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5109", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"189596 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4309", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67488 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"912", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"747224 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8122", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"219072 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2608", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83398 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1127", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"698556 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7593", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"485628 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7358", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57204 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2724", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74175 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4945", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93210 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3585", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"480998 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5593", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"777114 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9477", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"519025 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7985", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"183434 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4474", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"170724 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2082", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"270858 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6449", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"74520 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4140", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67782 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1738", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"165022 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6347", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"154105 : 85 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1813", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267080 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6070", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"184992 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7708", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"161840 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"136556 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"146170 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1555", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"217890 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75296 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2896", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1958 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"22", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54270 : 90 = ?","answers":[{"value":"603", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"299430 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5545", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"176792 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3157", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"182637 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4683", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"216270 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4005", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8780 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"439", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56576 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3328", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"323920 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4049", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"67332 : 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"724", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"186783 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2707", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267050 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2725", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"206505 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5295", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"877990 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9242", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"61465 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"647", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"289645 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5465", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"342930 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7455", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"582426 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7467", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41250 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1650", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"246420 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8214", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"545468 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5929", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"298232 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6778", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"493210 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6665", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153792 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2403", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"184800 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3080", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"404292 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4813", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"504774 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8703", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"168140 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6005", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"681002 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6949", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9541 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"329", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"567812 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5794", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"563762 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9242", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45600 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"600", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130906 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2257", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73260 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2442", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"553413 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7581", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"170730 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9485", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"335200 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4190", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"353722 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4982", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"273933 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8301", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"149750 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5990", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"351144 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"170784 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3558", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128072 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9148", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"37788 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"402", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"340186 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3619", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"697977 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8617", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"317684 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3694", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"207698 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7162", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"123984 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5904", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6279 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"273", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158184 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4056", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104546 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4021", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"222860 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5065", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"273896 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9782", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"553012 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6011", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"177882 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7734", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"505062 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9353", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"249816 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8922", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"253012 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5884", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24462 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1359", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"98874 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3662", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"21549 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"653", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"577792 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9472", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"228528 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36939 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1759", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"821826 : 89 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9234", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"373838 : 94 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3977", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"219180 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2810", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"62048 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1108", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"52104 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2171", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"514962 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8442", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"267665 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3995", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"542938 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9361", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6810 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"454", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"227040 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4730", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"105840 : 84 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1260", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"143568 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1994", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"268960 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6560", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"125378 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1529", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65680 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4105", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"454145 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7445", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"41616 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"867", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"533194 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9193", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"261738 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7074", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"114390 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3690", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59010 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1686", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16150 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"425", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"193868 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5702", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65072 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"784", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"604640 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7558", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"608028 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8812", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"158592 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1652", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"103950 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1890", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"166240 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8312", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"430352 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8276", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"248880 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3111", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"491304 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7444", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2016 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"28", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160797 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7657", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"538412 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6566", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"393120 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6240", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"229706 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2671", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"453720 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5970", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"356330 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5482", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"472122 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7494", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"128051 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1663", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"152160 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9510", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"59307 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1119", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"153476 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2257", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"249930 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8331", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"555872 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9584", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"364572 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9348", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"141210 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3138", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"254696 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9796", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"287070 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9569", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"377692 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3854", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"569291 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9649", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"57816 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1606", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10356 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"863", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16169 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"851", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3140 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"157", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"694966 : 86 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8081", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"273636 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4146", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"51870 : 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3990", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"360270 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8006", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"611442 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7839", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72908 : 11 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6628", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"276136 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9862", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"234952 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5464", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"396600 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6610", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"504573 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6387", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"339521 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6929", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"93412 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4246", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"134235 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7065", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"182336 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4144", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"73437 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1883", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"247194 : 93 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2658", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"337440 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4218", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"108848 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6803", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"38808 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"882", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54450 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3630", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10625 : 85 = ?","answers":[{"value":"125", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106000 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2000", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30051 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1113", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"401898 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4101", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"839705 : 95 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8839", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"512720 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8840", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"322840 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5765", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"127320 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5305", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"216216 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4158", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"272020 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7772", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"111612 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9301", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"272580 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6490", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"33969 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"507", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"32796 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"911", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"151145 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3515", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"183679 : 83 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2213", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56370 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3758", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"116136 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9678", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45122 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2051", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"75257 : 13 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5789", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100947 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1463", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"256080 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6402", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65552 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1928", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"885521 : 91 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9731", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"672888 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9752", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11300 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"452", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24556 : 14 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1754", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"519400 : 98 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5300", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50460 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2523", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"424120 : 92 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4610", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"164274 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8646", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"517260 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8621", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"115884 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9657", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13900 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"278", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"847776 : 96 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8831", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"279510 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6655", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"83996 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1909", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"231921 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3177", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"159866 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4207", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"104820 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6988", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"143374 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7546", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"130235 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3721", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50940 : 12 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4245", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"135412 : 97 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1396", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10215 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"227", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"490770 : 82 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5985", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"198588 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7638", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"106191 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1311", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"124320 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3552", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"65518 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1927", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"410298 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9769", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"294066 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4743", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"192375 : 81 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2375", "hint":"Ответ?"}]}
